Now that you've seen how to take a first pass at choosing high-level metrics,
现在 你了解了在选择高级指标时如何筛选
it's time to get some practice.
接下来我们进行一些实践
I'm going to describe some of the experiments Audacity is considering, and
我会描述一些 Audacity 正在考虑的实验
for each one, I want you to choose the metric you think would make the best
我想让你们针对每个实验选择出你认为
primary metric to evaluate that experiment.
评估实验最好的主要指标
The first experiment that Audacity runs changes the course list page.
Audacity 运行的第一个实验是修改课程列表页面
Each course has a short description on this page, and
在这个页面上每门课程都有一个简要描述
Audacity tests updating one of these descriptions.
Audacity 测试每条描述的更新
The second experiment is to increase the size of the Start Now button
第二个实验是将 Audacity 主页上
on Audacity's homepage.
“现在开始”按钮变大
And the third experiment is to add additional text to the site, explaining
第三个实验是在网站上增加文本
what the coaches do, and what other benefits come with the paid service.
解释辅导服务 付费服务的其他一些好处是什么
Now, for each of these experiments,
现在 我会针对每个实验
I'm going to give you some metrics to choose form.
给出一些可供选择的指标
Your first choice is the click-through-rate on the Start Now
你的第一选择是主页上“现在开始”按钮
button on the homepage.
的点击率
Since the Start Now button is the only way of progressing from the homepage to
因为“现在开始”按钮是从主页到课程列表的唯一途径
the course list, this metric is also the rate at which users progress from
这个指标也是用户
the top level of our funnel we talked about previously, to the second level.
从我们之前谈到的漏斗的第一个等级到第二个等级的比率
The second metric you can choose is the click-through-probability
可供选择的第二个指标是
of the Start Now button.
“现在开始”按钮的点击概率
That is, the probability of progressing from the homepage to the course list.
也就是从主页到课程列表的概率
The third metric you can choose is the probability that a student progresses
可供选择的第三个指标是学员
from the course list to a specific course page.
从课程列表到某个课程页面的概率
That's related to the probability that a user progresses from
这与用户从漏斗第二个等级
the second to the third level of our funnel.
到第三个等级的概率有关
But note that it's not quite the same because this third level is the visit to
但要注意 这并不完全一样 因为第三个等级是访问
any course page, and depending on the experiment,
任一课程页面 根据实验
you might want to choose this to be a specific course page.
你可能想选择某一个特定的课程页面
The fourth metric you can choose is the probability of progressing from
可供选择的第四个指标是
a specific course to enrolling in that course.
从一门特定课程到注册这门课程的概率
Again, this is related to, but not the same as, the probability of progressing
再强调一遍 这与从漏斗的这个等级到这个等级的概率相关 但却不相同
from this level of the funnel to this level, since you might want to compute
因为你可能想要针对某门专门的课程计算这个指标
this metric for a specific course, rather than across all courses.
而不是针对所有课程
And the fifth metric you can track is the probability that
你能够跟踪的第五个指标是
an enrolled student starts using or paying for coaching, the paid service.
注册学员使用或支付辅导这一付费服务的概率
Now, like Diane and Carrie mentioned, for most experiments,
现在 就像 Diane 和 Carrie 所提到的 对于大多数实验
you'll actually want to track more than one metric.
实际上你想要跟踪的不止一个指标
For this quiz,
对于这道测试题
choose one of these metrics for each experiment as the primary metric for
为每个实验选择一个指标作为这个实验的主要指标
that experiment, and write the number of your your choice in these boxes.
然后在这些条形框里写下你选择的选项编号
Please also discuss on the forums,
请在论坛上讨论
what additional metrics you would want to track for each experiment.
你想为每个实验跟踪的其他指标是什么
You might want to track more than one metric from the list, or
你可能想跟踪这个列表中的多个指标
you might think of other metrics you're interested in tracking.
或者 你还可以提出你想要跟踪的其他指标